1st edition continues!
Yay!
Yes, so hello everyone!
It's us, Natai Karumee!
Our regular big project!
This time, we would like to decide who is the most knowledgeable member about the human eye!
Good luck!
By the way, so far, we have decided King Honda, King Nagata, King Suganami, and King Kawaguchi.
The Honda King is Moiko Kamisawa, the Nagata King is Miyuki Honda, the Suganami King is Hana Koike, and the Kawaguchi Natsune King is Momo-chan Sakurai, respectively!
Momo Sakurai was the winner, but were you there too?
Milten was there too!
Hold the minus point for Milten!
I learned that negative points can be attached.
Not today!
If you do something weird, I can give you a minus point!
What do you think? Are you confident?
I'd like to say I'm confident, but I like this girl too much!
I don't know!
I don't know if this is a relevant question!
I don't know what she likes or what she's into at the moment.
I don't know!
I'll do my best!
Mr. Nagata, please continue!
Here is the first question!
What is your most enjoyable memory of 2023?
What? What is it?
Did I have a good time this year?
We did a lot.
Yes, we did.
So, I'm going to change it up a little bit.
What?
Can you tell me about it in your book?
Like, something fun that you've been doing lately.
Something fun?
Recently?
We were all there, but...
We were all here.
We can't go there yet.
We were all here, weren't we?
We were all here.
Wait, I might go on for a bit.
No.
I mean, it's the most fun I've had recently.
No, my project.
My project.
I've been having the most fun lately.
What the heck!
Yes, I did!
Oh, you went?
Seino
Yes!
Oh! Moomikai... oh, wait! This is it! This is it!
What do you think? It's definitely the one!
Hmm...
Maybe it's something else now.
Wait, it's absolutely right!
Here is the correct answer!
On the location bus going to work,
Aah!
Um, he's the one who played the game.
Wow! There it is! There it is!
That's it!
He was having so much fun that he was taking this picture of everyone's overhead.
Hayano's voice was the loudest this year,
He was singing the whole time,
He was singing the whole time, wasn't he?
This is the first time for Shi-chan. Driving in the bus.
For sure! Indeed!
One point for winning the bus, right?
Yes!
Good job on the drinking!
That was fun! Everyone had a normal drinking party, didn't they?
Yes! Here is the second question!
What kind of Suzuki bite do you hate!
What kind?
At home!
But I also find this difficult,
I'm like this, and I don't like it if it's the other way around.
Yes, I understand.
You mean the opposite of the usual, right?
Everyone is in order, right?
Here are our answers.
Jan!
Oh! This way.
Weak pressure
Interesting.
Weak Pressure
I don't like Coke
I don't like Coke.
What's that?
But I think you're right.
Here's the answer.
I don't like Kazumi Suzuki who is too indecisive.
Good, she's more indecisive than I thought.
Too much!
Then our answer is better.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Gyakuatsu is the best.
You're looking very bright today, aren't you?
Maybe I am.
I'll decide pretty clearly.
It's obvious it's a key.
I get a lot of questions about it, but I've got it all figured out.
It's been decided from the beginning.
Don't even say it's all decided.
I'm sorry.
So the second question was answered incorrectly.
All of you answered incorrectly.
Now, here's the third question.
Please pour me a hot sauce.
What did you say?
You saw the same person as usual?
Yes, exactly like that. I think you'll probably get it right.
Maybe it's easy.
I'm often asked to pour it on.
Often.
I don't understand why they ask you to pour hot sauce on them.
Let's start with me.
Yes, it happened.
It's hot.
I'm at the door.
I'm with you.
Oh, yes, yes, you're doing it.
Oh, I'm going to say it.
I'm going to say all of them.
So here is the correct answer.
What?
I say "atz" but I don't say "atz".
I don't say "atz.
I only say "yes.
I'll get to that later.
I didn't say anything.
When I said I was going to do it with lines.
This is what I was getting at.
Wait a minute.
0.5 points.
Yay!
That's great!
So Shiori got 0.5 points all by herself!
Congratulations!
That's great!
The fourth question is as follows
What is your favorite music video?
What?
Isn't this one hard?
It's hard.
Isn't it?
Hii likes it.
I've heard of this one.
I can't choose just one.
Okay, here are my answers.
Go on, go on, go on.
You looking at me
It was your sound
Hitomi and
Oh!
I feel like I've heard that before.
I like all the music videos, but I've never said it.
You don't say all of them.
Here's the correct answer.
It's "Magical Bastarisk.
What?
That's it after all.
I thought so.
No, that lip scene leaked.
It was so cute!
You were so cute.
You know, I couldn't choose.
I couldn't pick one... because the lip scene was leaked... and because I personally like the song.
And I really like the song.
She said it was her favorite song.
It was a one-shot.
That's why I made you get up so deep.
Okay, the current score for the fourth question is
Miru-chan has 0 points
1 point for Kana
1.5 points for Chi-chan
Oooh!
There's still a chance for the bag
I think there is
There still is.
So here is the fifth question
Is there anything you'd like to take this opportunity to apologize to your manager for?
Oh, I know.
I'm like BACLOS.
I look like a BACLOS!
Wait a minute, everybody calm down.
Shush.
That's as far as you can go.
As far as I can tell, I'm in love with you.
Oh my God, oh my God!
Let me say I said it.
Let me say something bad.
I don't like it.
Not at all.
I was just talking to the manager.
I thought this might be it.
You go ahead, Miru-chan.
I'm sorry I left my stuff on loan.
What are you writing?
Please give it back.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
Yes, I'm here.
I don't get my blog out by the deadline.
I've never done it before.
Oh, wait.
Wait, last time I did it, I did it a day before the deadline.
That's great.
Wait a minute.
How long have we been blogging?
I know, I really do.
I think about this all the time.
I'm sorry.
Well, Chi...
How about you, Mr. Chi?
I'm sorry for opening too much of my luggage.
I have a lot of stuff.
I'm not sure if the members would do it.
That's right.
I apologize.
Well, here's the correct answer.
I'm sorry for always asking for favors.
In remembrance of this.
0.5 points for the social aspect.
Here is the sixth question.
What do you like about Cobb that you've been selling for years?
He's cute.
I don't know if I like him.
You'll like it.
I'm not flirting.
That's what you keep saying, isn't it?
You've been acting like a grandma to people lately.
Yeah.
You're like a granddaughter to the alien members.
Yes, I really do.
I still love my grandchildren.
They're my grandchildren.
I'm raising them.
Well, let's get it in order, shall we?
Let's finish up.
Let's start with you, Miru-chan.
You're a cool dancer, baby, and you're cute.
I have three.
I have two, too.
So sweet and soothing.
adorable and healty
So cute
He gives me so much, it's embarrassing.
You're talking too much.
No, that's not it.
That's what I say when I can't get close enough to fix it.
Make an air bank.
He says, "Your face is really small.
That's probably not it.
What are you adding?
Well, here's the correct answer.
I like that it's the complete opposite of my personality.
That's right.
I know.
I can see that.
The way you think and the things you like.
I feel like we're the complete opposites.
And the things you like, too.
On the contrary, I find those things attractive.
Like the way you think.
I'm saying this a lot, too.
2.5 points
This too? I did it.
I'm saying it.
I might have said that to the other girls.
I did.
Thank you. We're in five.
And now for the seventh question.
The real one.
Read one.
Did you write "one" in five, seven, five?
Yes, sir.
Did you know five, seven, five?
I think it's hard.
It was really hard.
It was difficult.
That's how this came about.
How long did it take you to figure it out?
About 30 seconds.
So it's a spur-of-the-moment kind of thing.
No extra characters, right?
Okay, let's answer one at a time.
Here we go.
Thank you for your kindness.
Thank you very much!
Thank you, Peco!
You're right, you're right.
You really are an idiot!
MIRUMIRUMIRUMIRUMIRUMIRUMIRUMIRUMIRUMIRUMIRU
MIRUMIRUMIRUMIRUMIRUMIRUMIRUMIRUMIRUMIRUMIRUMIRUMIRUMIRU
You're serious.
That's right.
I'm off.
Thanks for the quick reply, Miruten.
That's great.
I get set up a lot.
You're a real help.
What's the right answer?
What?
Mimi-mimi-mimi.
Milky-White.
You already got it.
Wait a minute.
It's not here.
It's right there.
It's not even stretched.
It's right here.
It's right, isn't it?
0.3 points.
We got 0.3 points.
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Really?
Milten's there.
575 is wonderful.
I gave you 0.5 points.
I got something.
I got you something.
It'll help me with my early transformation.
I'm out.
Last question.
As of now, you have 1.8 points.
I have 1.8 points
Chi-chan has 2 points.
Chi-chan is leading.
No one has a minus.
Oh, I made a mistake.
Chi-chan.
So, the 8th question is
This way.
I'm reading the question.
Orihana and
Kana Finn, where are you two going on your date?
What do you do?
Our World
I wonder
Outside
indoors
I can't say either way, can I?
I don't think so.
I can tell.
One day.
A whole day.
We're stopping this early.
It's done.
Wait a minute.
Shi-chan, you first.
I like it with curry balls.
It's like she's waiting.
By the way, Hana-chan and
Hitomi is a snow body
I'm often asked about it.
Snow body
And now, Mil-chan.
The End
Branding in Hokkaid
It's that time of the year again
I'm here Ginza Onsen Hot Springs Snowboarding
The correct answer is...
We promised to go to the silver mine. We started last year.
Let's go.
We've got two wins and two losses.
I'm sorry.
I don't know how many times I've said it.
We talked about this weeks ago.
Speaking of saying it, here it is.
Yes, that's right.
And since you got the location right...
That's 100 points.
That's what I'm talking about.
Both of you.
So...
The score is
On one.
The number of points is
Miru-chan has 1 point
2 points for Chi-chan
Hana has 2 points
Hana is O!
It means that the bond of love is strong.
This is the next
what the life of King Ogi Hana will be like.
You'd think, wouldn't you?
All the oohs and billin
I'm sorry if I can't make it.
I'm in first place, so...
Congratulations.
Let's go.
You two.
It was a close race.
It's easy to see.
I guess you could say that.
Well, that's all for now.
I'm King Suzuki.
Bye bye.